[Music]
even when production doesn't go as plann
it is important to keep your inventory
cost and financial transactions accurate
in this release we are adding capability
to revert output or consumption
transactions return unused raw materials
back to the
warehouse or correct mistakes in the
capacity Ledger entries what if you
discovered mistake after changing status
of production order to finished you can
reopen finished production order and
make necessary adjustment and then
finish it again let's see it in the demo
Begin by examining the end stage of
production the finished production order
the document attachment is absent output
is incomplete additionally exploring
value Ledger entries reveals a
significantly high capacity in
consumption resulting in wrong cost to
produced items
to address this issue choose the reopen
action this action will redirect you to
the restored release production
order Begin by uploading the required
file The Next Step involves Examining
The Ledger entries first navigate to the
capacity Ledger entry select the entry
with high capacity and choose the
reverse production order transaction
which will generate a transaction with a
negative quantity and populate all other
relevant
Fields repeat the operation on the item
Ledger entries where output or
consumption can be canceled we cancel
consumption and we got raw materials
back on the stock and there is an
application between these two so cost is
properly
considered fix the missing post by going
to the production
Journal then change the status to
finished the finished production order
now has an attachment explore the item
Ledger entry to verify that the output
entries reflect accurate quantities and
costs impressive in the next demo we
will explore how to deal with mistakes
involving subcontracting also we will
learn how to close orders and write off
accumulated work in progress in case the
real scrap
ured let's use the demo in this scenario
we have a release production order with
finished quantity because it involves
subcontracting for some operations
including the final routing line we need
to cancel it
differently navigate to the purchase
order and open the receipt select both
lines linked to the production order and
choose undo due
receipt close the receipt and delete the
purchase
order return to the release production
order to see that the output is reverted
consumption remains unchanged and must
be canceled manually we will keep the
consumption as we want to explore a
scenario where the production order has
capacity or component consumption but no
output the amounts accumulated in the
work and progress account need to be
written off first enable the ability to
finish production orders without output
in the manufacturing setup page change
the status of the release production
order to finished and activate the
finishing order toggle once the order is
finished review the general ledger
entries
the accumulated amounts from the work in
progress account have been transferred
to the inventory adjustment account
thank you for watching you can learn
more about capability in the release
notes you can find the link in the
description also remember to watch other
videos about enhancements on
manufacturing area